He's clean. He's mean. He's the go-between.
St. Ives is a action, crime, thriller film directed by J. Lee Thompson.
A dabbler-in-crime and his assistant hire an ex-police
reporter to recover some stolen papers.
Raymond St. Ives, played by Charles Bronson.
Abner Procane, played by John Houseman.
Janet Whistler, played by Jacqueline Bisset.
Dr. John Constable, played by Maximilian Schell.
Det. Frank Deal, played by Harry Guardino.
Det. Carl Oller, played by Harris Yulin.
Ives is a 1976 American crime thriller film directed by J.
Lee Thompson and starring Charles Bronson, John Houseman,
Jacqueline Bisset, and Maximilian Schell.
The film was the first of nine collaborations between Bronson and director J.
Lee Thompson.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
swimming pool, shootout, gunfight, writer.
The tone is intense.